<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Sudoku Light</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_undo">Undo</string>

    <string-array name="types_name">
        <item>Last Value</item>
        <item>Hidden Single in Box</item>
        <item>Hidden Single in Box 2</item>
        <item>Hidden Single in Row/Column</item>
        <item>Naked Single</item>
        <item>Naked Single 2</item>
        <item>Locked Candidates</item>
        <item>Pairs</item>
        <item>Bivalue Universal Grave</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="introduction_message">
        <item>1.In Sudoku, you place a number from 1 to 9 in each blank cell.</item>
        <item>3.Each rows (there are nine rows), and columns (there are also nine columes) contain numbers from 1 through 9.</item>
        <item>4.Also, 3x3 blocks bounded by bold lines (nine blocks) contain numbers from 1 through 9.</item>
        <item>5.This is an example of answer. Lock at the top row colored in light blue. Each cell in the line contains numbers 1 through 9.</item>
        <item>6.Please check the left column colored in blue also contain every number from 1 to 9.</item>
        <item>7.And, the colored 3x3 block contains numbers from 1 to 9.</item>
        <item>8.Checking numbers helps you to find a good starting point. First, look at rows and columns.</item>
        <item>9.Since, as for the 3x3 block on the left hand-side, 1 is already contained in the upper row and middle at the right, therefore, 1 is not placed in the cell.</item>
        <item>10.Would be the only cell that wounld contain 1.</item>
        <item>11.In this figure, 1 goes into similarly.</item>
        <item>12.Also in this figure, 1 goes into.</item>
        <item>13.Again, 1 goes into.</item>
        <item>15.Here is a little tip for advanced folks. As you can see, in top left 3x3 block, there are two cells that may contain 1.</item>
        <item>16.One of the should have 1, So that you cannot place 1 in blue cells.</item>
        <item>17.Since 1 does not go into the blue cell, you can safely assume that 1 goes into.</item>
        <item>18.There are many more tips.Try discovering your own as you go along.</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="types">
        <item>901</item>
        <item>911</item>
        <item>912</item>
        <item>913</item>
        <item>921</item>
        <item>922</item>
        <item>931</item>
        <item>941</item>
        <item>951</item>
    </integer-array>

    <item name="data_base_data" type="id"/>
    <item name="data_base_id" type="id"/>
    <item name="REQUEST_CODE" type="id"/>
    <item name="RESULT_CODE_OK" type="id"/>

    <string name="success">Success</string>

</resources>